arena-multimedia.com 2018-07-08

# Privacy Policy - Arena Animation

  * Home
  * Privacy Policy

We do not sell or forward or rent your personal information what you share with Aptech, to any third party for any purposes like marketing etc. without your consent. This privacy policy is applicable to our services available under the aforesaid domain names. Your use of Aptech Site will signify your acceptance of the Aptech Privacy Policy.

Wherever your Personal Information is held within Aptech, the company shall take reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. Aptech is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information, we protect it through the use of encryption. 

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Aptech. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information then you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with Aptech, Aptech will continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.

Where Aptech gets your Personal Information on the Site, Aptech intends to explain why Personal Information will be collected and whether Aptech plans to share such Personal Information outside or with those working on Aptech's behalf. Unless the transfer of Personal Information is legally required, Aptech will not transfer Personal Information without your permission to third parties.

In the event that you do provide Personal Information, Aptech shall maintain accurate Personal Information that you have provided. Where Aptech collects Personal Information from you on the Site, its aim is to provide a means of contacting Aptech whenever you need to update or correct that Information.

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only. We do not sell or rent Personal Information, except that your Personal Information shall be shared with our business partners/franchisees and you shall be deemed to have given consent to the same. We will share Personal Information only under the circumstances where we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so.

By using the Site, you consent to the terms of Aptech's Privacy Policy and processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. When your Personal information is needed, Aptech will not be obligated to let you know at the time of collection, how it will use the personal information. Generally the personal information Aptech collects is used only by it to respond to your inquiry, process an order or allow you to access specific services. You will be offered an opportunity to limit access to your information. In case Aptech does not receive any response from you to limit the access of your information, it shall be deemed that you consent to such distribution of your Personal Information as mentioned above.

Please note that this Privacy Policy may keep changing from time to time without notice at the sole discretion of Aptech. If you have any questions about Aptech Privacy Policy, collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please e-mail us at [digitalsolutions@aptech.ac.in.](mailto:digitalsolutions@aptech.ac.in "digital solutions")
